ezcater.com 2019-05-16

# Catering Services Near You - Order Online from ezCater

Effective Date: August 1, 2017

Guiding Principle _You control what we do with your personal information._

#### Introduction

This privacy policy describes how ezCater, Inc. collects and uses the personal information you provide on any of our websites (including our mobile websites) and on any of our mobile applications. It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information. In this policy, ezCater, we, us, and our all refer to ezCater, Inc.

If you have a privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at <https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request>.

#### What information do we collect and how do we use it?

So we can serve you, you give us information such as your contact, billing or payment information, and/or details about orders, client needs, or your menu and operation. In addition, we log interactions such as visits to our website, orders placed or discussed, and communications among you, us, and third parties such as customers, food providers, delivery companies, and delivery locations.

We use the information provided to create your profile, place orders with food providers to deliver food and services to whatever location(s) you designate, create food provider profiles, and communicate transaction-related messages, newsletters and promotional messages. To opt out of newsletters and promotional messages, please follow the directions in the newsletters and promotional messages, or change your account preferences in your Profile page.

We share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We may provide your personal information to companies who help us help you. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide their services. For instance, if you are a customer, we communicate your billing details to a payment processor, and your order details to the food provider, any delivery service, and perhaps also to the party receiving the food. If you choose to designate an alternate contact person, we will share the alternate contact information with these parties. If you came to us through a link supplied to you by a food provider, we communicate your contact information to the food provider, who may use it to market to you. If you place orders for your employer, and your employer is an ezCater 'enterprise user' or 'corporate account' or ‘national account’, we may share your information with your employer. If you are a food provider, we communicate your payment details to a payment processor, and your menu and operating constraints to customers and prospects, any delivery service, and any other parties needed to process any orders you receive or might receive. If you are a delivery service, we communicate your contact information to food providers as needed to process any pick-ups or deliveries you receive or might receive.

We may use your contact (but never your billing or payment) information to send you communications regarding our products and services. We may share your contact (but never your billing or payment) information with selected third parties whose offers we believe you may value. To opt out of this sharing, please change your account preferences in your Profile page.

If you are the recipient of food ordered through ezCater, your delivery-related information and dietary needs or preferences may be communicated to food providers, delivery companies, or other parties as needed so they can serve you.

#### How do we protect your information?

We use state-of-the-art protection. All password and billing information you provide on our websites or mobile applications is transmitted via a secure connection called "Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) with 128-bit encryption", and then stored in a secure environment. The only credit card information we store is a credit card number's last four digits.

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee absolute security of your information. Please contact us if you have any questions about security on our websites or mobile applications.

#### What tracking technologies do we use?

Technologies such as cookies or similar technologies are used by ezCater and our partners. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for _nothing other than to make the ordering process faster._ Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

As is true of most websites, applications, and similar technologies, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, Internet service providers (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating systems, date/time stamps, and clickstream data.

We may combine this automatically-collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve your experience with ezCater, and the content for the communications we send to you.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out at [http://preferences-mgr.truste.com](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/). Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

#### You control your information

Upon request ezCater will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You can always edit and delete your information in your Profile page. On that page (or via email to [support@ezcater.com](mailto:support@ezcater.com)), you can also opt into or out of our sharing of your personal information with certain third parties. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

We reserve the right to use for ourselves, and to convey to third parties, information that has been modified so the information cannot be traced back to a specific person or company.

We may disclose your personal information (i) as required by law, in response to lawful requests by public authorities, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; (ii) when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; and (iii) to any third party with your prior consent to do so. We may transfer your information in the course of a corporate divestiture, merger, or dissolution. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our websites and mobile applications of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. Please contact us if you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

#### Other

We are not responsible in any way for websites linked to or from ours. Our policies are in effect only when you are actually on our websites or mobile applications. That means that when you link to another website or mobile application, our policies will not be in effect on that other website or mobile application. Similarly, if you reach us through a link from another website, mobile application, email, or any other source not controlled by us, our policies will not have been in effect on that other source. We recommend that you understand the policies of the other website, application, or other entity before proceeding.

Our websites and mobile applications include social media features (such as the Facebook Like button) and widgets (such as the ShareThis button or other interactive mini-programs). These features may collect your IP address and information about which page you are visiting on our sites or mobile applications, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the features, regardless of whether these features and widgets are hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our websites or mobile applications.

Our websites and mobile applications give you the ability to leave reviews for orders. These reviews may, solely at our option, be made publicly accessible. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. If you wish to edit or change these reviews you may do so by accessing the order where you originally left the review. To request removal of a review, please contact us at [support@ezcater.com](mailto:support@ezcater.com).

Our websites and mobile applications give you the ability to leave comments that may, solely at our option, be made publicly accessible through a third party provider. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. You may not be able to edit or change such comments. To request removal of a comment, or of your personal information from a comment, please contact us or the third party provider. We may not be able to remove your personal information. We will let you know if we are unable to do so, and why.

If you use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, you will give us your friend’s name and email address. We will send your friend a series of emails inviting him or her to visit our site. We store your friend’s information for the purpose of sending these emails and tracking the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us at [support@ezcater.com](mailto:support@ezcater.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

If you choose to suggest a food provider to us, you will give us the food provider’s name, location, and phone number. We store the food provider’s information so we can reach out to the suggested food provider. The food provider may contact us at [support@ezcater.com](mailto:support@ezcater.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

If you are a food provider, we may list you in our publicly accessible directory. If you wish to request removal of your information from our directory, you can contact us at [support@ezcater.com](mailto:support@ezcater.com). If you provide us information about your business, we will use and store that information to service and support you. The profile you create, or we create for you, on our websites or through our mobile applications will be publicly accessible unless you request to be removed from our websites and mobile applications.

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on the site or application where you are reading this, prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Us

Please never hesitate to email us at [support@ezcater.com](mailto:support@ezcater.com) or call us at 1-800-488-1803.

ezCater, Inc.  
101 Arch Street  
Suite 1510  
Boston, MA 02110
